<packageInfo>
    <bundleId>com.joey-gm.artemis</bundleId>
    <name>Artemis</name>
    <version>0.7.21~beta5</version>
    <descriptions>
        <description>
            Springboard UI customization
        </description>
        <description>
            Create a simplistic and clutter-free home screen and lock screen experience on iOS 13. 
        </description>
        <description>
            Configurable options: 
        </description>
        <description>
            - Hide home bar indicator
        </description>
        <description>
            - Home screen: transparent dock, page indicator, hide or rename icon labels, hide recently updated dots, undim screen timed out icon, hide the hourglass label
        </description>
        <description>
            - Lock screen: remove Face ID lock icon, control center grabber, quick action buttons, 'no older notification' prompt, customize unlock hint, disable charging animation
        </description>
        <description>
            - Status bar: rename carrier, wifi network as carrier name, hide carrier, hide all status bar items
        </description>
        <description>
            - Spotlight search: disable search bar on home screen and/or lock screen's today view
        </description>
        <description>
            - Today View: hide widget edit button, hide widget background and remove weather and stocks footer's info from today view.
        </description>
        <description>
            Experimental feature: mini media control on lock screen (tested on iPhone X only; may lead to undesirable layout on other phone resolutions)
        </description>
    </descriptions>
    <compatibility>
        <miniOS>13.0</miniOS>
        <maxiOS>13.3</maxiOS>
    </compatibility>
    <changelog>
        <change>
            <changeVersion>V0.7.21 (beta 5)</changeVersion>
            <changeDescription>Wifi network as carrier name, hide widget background and some under the hood code optimizations.</changeDescription>
        </change>
        <change>
            <changeVersion>V0.7.21 (beta 4)</changeVersion>
            <changeDescription>Disable charging animation, hide recently updated dots, remove widget edit button and footer from Today View.</changeDescription>
        </change>
        <change>
            <changeVersion>V0.7.21 (beta 3)</changeVersion>
            <changeDescription>Screen Time: Undim timed out icon and hide the hourglass label.</changeDescription>
        </change>
        <change>
            <changeVersion>V0.7.21 (beta 2)</changeVersion>
            <changeDescription>New options for status bar and spotlight search.</changeDescription>
            <changeDescription>Unlock hint customization applies to both 'Swipe up to open' (iPhone X+) and 'Press home button to unlock' (home button devices).</changeDescription>
        </change>
        <change>
            <changeVersion>V0.7.21 (beta 1)</changeVersion>
            <changeDescription>Initial public release.</changeDescription>
        </change>
    </changelog>
    <screenshots>
        <screen>1.PNG</screen>
        <screen>2.PNG</screen>
        <screen>3.PNG</screen>
    </screenshots>
</packageInfo>
